<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hacking on ~/rodnt</title>
    <link>https://rodnt.github.io/categories/hacking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hacking on ~/rodnt</description>
    <generator>$() -- go$().io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 17:12:34 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://rodnt.github.io/categories/hacking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Detect burp suite</title>
      <link>https://rodnt.github.io/posts/2023-01-01-detect-burp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 17:12:34 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rodnt.github.io/posts/2023-01-01-detect-burp/</guid>
      <description>tl;dr&#xA;You can see the result here :)&#xA;Click here 👀&#xA;Hey guys, I’m here to show you a little simple technique, but it’s a tip that maybe someday help someone. The question is how to identify that someone is using web proxy (BURP)? well, a friend of mine aka Jerry was with me one afternoon and we decided to do a PoC, maybe a lot of people already know, but when starting BURP it automatically goes up to a “light” web server where you can for example download the BURP certificate to import into your browser or device at the following address http://burp/ The following image illustrates this interface:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS Anti-Tampers Bypass</title>
      <link>https://rodnt.github.io/posts/ios-anti-tampers-bypass/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 17:12:34 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rodnt.github.io/posts/ios-anti-tampers-bypass/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone, in this blog i&amp;rsquo;m going to explain a little bit of my journey to solve a iOS challenge proposed by @as0ler. The Challenge can be found at the following link:&#xA;https://github.com/hexploitable/r2con2020_r2frida/blob/master/ios-challenge-2.ipa The challenge is to remove all anti-tamper methods, that means you will have to remove some methods such as:&#xA;ptrace sysctl strstr geppid In this blog, I will only talk about how I did it to bypass, using only frida with radare2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SQL Injection CVE-2022-23046 - PHPIPAM &#43; Exploit</title>
      <link>https://rodnt.github.io/posts/2022-01-20-cve_2022_23046_phpipam/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 17:12:34 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rodnt.github.io/posts/2022-01-20-cve_2022_23046_phpipam/</guid>
      <description>CVE-2022-23046 - PHPIPAM TL;DR&#xA;This write up is about a SQL injection which I found 4 days after another researcher reported it :/, however, because of the fact that I haven’t found any write ups or publicly available exploits, I decided to write about it. Exploit at the end!&#xA;PHPIPAM is a software widely used internally by several companies. And by being so, it is relatively common for you to find a running instance to manage IT assets, networks, etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SQL Injection WAF bypass techniques</title>
      <link>https://rodnt.github.io/posts/2020-12-12-sqli-bypass.techs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 17:12:34 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rodnt.github.io/posts/2020-12-12-sqli-bypass.techs/</guid>
      <description>HI, People In this basic tutorial, I want to show you a little bit of SQL Injection WAF bypass, I know it is a subject that is well commented and discussed every day .. after all, WAFS are boring :/ and in the end .. they just work as a superficial protection for an environment (in my opnion it is like a leaky bucket that you fix with bubble gum) .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bypass NAC ( Network Access Control )</title>
      <link>https://rodnt.github.io/posts/2020-02-02-bypass-nac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 17:12:34 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rodnt.github.io/posts/2020-02-02-bypass-nac/</guid>
      <description>In this post i’ll describe how to bypass NAC ( Network Access Control ). During an internal pentest, I had a problem connecting to the client network ( all network devices 802.1x (including VoIP devices), after a few hours trying to find out why, I found out that the client had implemented NAC, but what is Network access protocol (NAC) ?&#xA;Network Access Control (NAC) is a solution used on corporate networks to prevent, or even hinder, unauthorized hosts from accessing internally available services and systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RCE using Path Traversal</title>
      <link>https://rodnt.github.io/posts/2020-01-02-rce-path-traversal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 17:12:34 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rodnt.github.io/posts/2020-01-02-rce-path-traversal/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, in this post i’ll describe how i used path traversal to explore a file upload, that enable me an RCE, during a private pentesting. I’ll blur the sensitive contents.&#xA;firstly, while browsing i found a paramater that caugth my attention, frameManagerPath a base64 parameter. This path always return a javascript code. like the image bellow:&#xA;After decode the the value, i could notice that value was a relative path to a file.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
